[Music]
My daughter's poetry
date Each patient should be completed Regularly do
two Tilaks of Qazi
[Music]
City recitation should be done
You should complete each Zardari
ICICI proof Dry prosperity animals
You have a pearl amount of Jamun in your planned wadi
You only could fulfill your muthat muthe dream
ICICI proof Sukh
Samriddhi Shobha Kavyacha Bhavan certified You
only could see your mulanchi muthe dream I could fulfill this
plan Jhalamsam synonym oil
Many benefits
rate-wise rupees
[Music]
Policy matures Jhalawar Yours goes
in tax free amount
Policy
meter
Sukh Samriddhi ji gives you your return Ji
full guarantee
Your each dream is with you Reena Re I have
faith and trust ICICI Prudential
Life Insurance
[Music]